linuxandubuntu.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy - LinuxAndUbuntu

## Who we are

Our website address is: http://www.linuxandubuntu.com.

We share applications, themes, icons and scripts, most of the stuff belong outside of linuxandubuntu.com and copyright owned by their respective owners. So we test applications and other stuff before releasing to the public. If you install something from linuxandubuntu.com, in that case, linuxandubuntu isn’t responsible for any loss/damage/discomfort occurred as a result of using stuff from linuxandubuntu (BTW we test everything at least once on our computers, we never release anything to the public if there are problems in Applications/stuff).

Any trademarks or logos used in this site are the property of their respective owners.

Any personal info provided to us, will not be shared with anyone outside linuxandubuntu.com. We don’t spam and never sell personal data to any individual/company/third-party.

linuxandubuntu.com isn’t responsible for externally linked sites. We recommend you to read the privacy policy of linked sites before disclosing any personal information to them.

 **Your browser  can turn-off our cookies or selectively third-party cookies or disable cookies within settings**

However, this step will affect your browser interaction with our website as well as other websites.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
